

Day of birth: 22/11/1993 Email: phanhuudinh@hotmail.com

Mobile: 0905221193

Address: 02 Cam Nam 9, Cam Le, Da Nang

Career Profile

I have almost 4 years of web programming experience as a fullstack developer with strong knowledge at both frontend and backend. Also have more than 1 year as a game programmer, that very helpful for me to power up up my skills in code performance and creative mindset.

Key Skills

Python/Django ReactJs
Golang SQL
Javascript HTML/CSS

Other Skills

Docker VueJs
Google Cloud Platform React Native
C#/Asp.net Firebase

Work Experience

Software Engineer at Orient Software

September 2018 - Present

Position: Developer / Team leader

Main stack: Django, ReactJs, PostgreSQL, GCP

Current stack: Golang, MySQL, GCP/AWS

- Discus and take requirement from customer
- o Analytic, design and development web app
- Manage some small project
- App Deployment
- Support teammate.

Web Developer at IOTLink 4DMap

Position: Developer

Main stack: C#/Asp.net, ReactJs, SQLServer, Microsoft Azure

November 2016 - September 2018

Web development bold client and server side for many in-sourcing project.

- Analytic, design and development web module
- Research and apply new technologies, techniques which useful and compatible with projects
- Development web api for mobile application
- App Deployment
- Support teammate.

2D/3D Game programmer at Gameloft

June 2015 - August 2016

Java 2D game creation

- Implement game actor follow design
- o Optimize performance for best quality and performance
- $\circ \quad \text{Support graphic-designer to use optimize tools.}$

C++/JAVA 3D Game publishing

- Implement anti hack/cheat for game
- Optimize and scale games for multy devices.

Education

HUE UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE

Grade: Good

Major: Informatics